{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["the", "him", "a", "Sometime"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: of", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["of", "search", "they", "take"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "mouse", "he", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lion", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["captured", "lion", "a", "and"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The _____________ was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["lion", "wagon", "search", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "went is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they _____________ in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lifted", "tied", "was", "went"]}, {"explanation": "tied is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and _____________ him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tied", "was", "went", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["After", "a", "that", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: able", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["idea", "able", "of", "him"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["after", "that", "of", "in"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["him", "to", "few", "a"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search _____________ a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "by", "of", "after"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["him", "to", "wagon", "that"]}, {"explanation": "go is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["let", "help", "take", "go"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["paw", "the", "him", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["and", "tickled", "help", "the"]}, {"explanation": "paw is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his _____________ and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["zoo", "lion", "idea", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["to", "a", "a", "later"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tickled", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tickled", "so", "and", "was"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Select appropiate Adverb from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["sometime", "later", "Sometime", "so"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["by", "that", "after", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: After", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["After", "went", "the", "to"]}, {"explanation": "zoo is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["search", "tree", "zoo", "paw"]}], "success": 1}